<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on keyboardcrunch</title>
    
    
    
    <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on keyboardcrunch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© keyboardcrunch</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 12:43:36 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking a Better SentinelOne</title>
      <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/hacking_a_better_sentinelone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 12:43:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/hacking_a_better_sentinelone/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          One of my few frustrations with modern EDR tooling are that most all of them have thrown out one of the most useful features of the legacy anti-virus, scanning of USB drives. They&amp;rsquo;re a vector for malicious files onto the network, files that could migrate to other places in your network before they&amp;rsquo;re ever analyzed, and this can possibly be an issue with compliance regulations (or at least a frustrated CISO as I experienced).
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommended SentinelOne Custom Detections</title>
      <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/recommended-sentinelone-custom-detections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:16:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/recommended-sentinelone-custom-detections/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Deep Visibility SentinelOne Deep Visibility has a very powerful language for querying on nearly any endpoint activity you&amp;rsquo;d want to dig up. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the Watchlist feature very heavily; from detecting common phishing Url patterns, unapproved software, insider threats, to LOLBAS activity. But very soon the Watchlist feature will be superseded by Custom Detections, basically Watchlist with ranking and remediation options.
The purpose of this post is to document a few top priority queries that go beyond the granular queries I&amp;rsquo;ve created and shared before.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCCM Baselines for SentinelOne</title>
      <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/sccm-baselines-sentinelone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 19:10:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/sccm-baselines-sentinelone/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          After a recent deployment to upgrade our SentinelOne agents I noticed a few unusual issues with agents; Agents offline in console, unresponsive agent module in Sentinelctl, SentinelAgent Windows service stuck in starting state. This may be specific to my organization&amp;rsquo;s environment, or our deployment method, but may also be due to changes to Anti-Tamper that restrict the use of 3rd party deployment tools through agents 4.6.2 - 4.6.12. On these systems the SentinelCtl.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun With Wireguard</title>
      <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/fun-with-wireguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 21:12:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/fun-with-wireguard/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          After a recent conversation I realized that some folks have a narrow view of what can be done with Wireguard, and VPN connections in general. Though recently a number of toolsets/frameworks tailored for networking of containers or &amp;ldquo;bolt on zero-trust&amp;rdquo; networking have expanded that perception. My goal with this post is to highlight some software leveraging Wireguard, and to list a few different use-cases and reasons for using Wireguard (over traditional VPN or ZeroTier).
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Security</title>
      <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/email-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 14:42:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/email-security/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          This post started as a quick note for securing email for unused domains but I decided I could expand upon it a bit more to define terms in a language I believe to be more clear than I&amp;rsquo;ve seen elsewhere, and from the view-point of an administrator or domain owner.
Index  SPF DMARC DKIM Securing Unused Domains Additional Resources  SPF Sender Policy Framework (SPF) is a method for defining domains or ips that are allowed to send email for your domain.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Static</title>
      <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/going-static/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 17:46:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/going-static/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          For the last few years I&amp;rsquo;ve been using either Wordpress or (usually) Ghost for my blogs, and self-hosting them. I&amp;rsquo;ve posted a mix of content including home-brewing, fermentation projects, posts describing code projects on my Github, and even rants and reviews. Due to a few failures on my part with backups and migrations, mainly with the images and static content, my blog has ended up missing some content and isn&amp;rsquo;t as clean as I&amp;rsquo;d like it to be.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>